<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Infusion-Therapy</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="demo_string">"Dr. J's Infusion Therapy reserves the right to refuse treatment to any client for any reason. Your IV Administrator may think that your symptoms appear to be more serious and require a higher level of care. Your IV Administrator may request that you call your doctor or go to the emergency department for further evaluation. It is ultimately your decision to do so and not doing so places you at risk. You understand this risk and accept all consequences if
you fail to do so.
I acknowledge that I cannot be treated by Dr. J's Infusion Therapy while I am actively consuming alcohol or under the medical treatment of another doctor for similar treatments. If I am actively intoxicated, I acknowledge that I will not be treated if I am unable to answer any and all questions used to determine my alertness and ability to make decisions for myself.
I agree to not use or tamper with the equipment, including the intravenous catheter, used by the staff at Dr. J's Infusion Therapy, I agree to not inject anything into this intravenous catheter, Directly injecting drugs or other things into this catheter can lead to overdose, infection, and death.

Dr. J's Infusion Therapy reserves the right to refuse treatment to any client for any reason. Your IV Administrator may think that your symptoms appear to be more serious and require a higher level of care. Your IV Administrator may request that you call your doctor or go to the emergency department for further evaluation. It is ultimately your decision to do so and not doing so places you at risk. You understand this risk and accept all consequences if
so.

I hereby grant permission to be treated for my symptoms, including, but not limited to: dehydration, headache, nausea, and vitamin deficiency, weight loss, etc. I understand
that this treatment does involve an IV (intravenous catheter). I understand that medical treatment involves risks. The most common risks from hydration therapy include, but are not limited to: allergic reaction to medications, vein irritation, heartburn, fluid overload, kidney problems, headache, and pain at the IV site. The rarer side effects include, but are not limited to: inflammation of the vein used for injection, phlebitis, metabolic disturbances and injury. The extremely rare side effects include, but are not limited to: severe allergic reaction, anaphylaxis, infection, cardiac arrest, and/or death. I have informed the IV Administrator of any known allergies to drugs or other substances, or of any past reactions to aesthetics. I have informed the IV Administrator of all current medications and supplements. I will also notify Prime IV Hydration And Wellness before any treatments are performed, of any changes in my medical status and/or changes in my medication(s).

I am aware that other unforeseeable conditions could occur. I do not expect the IV Administrator to anticipate and/or explain all risk and possible complications. I rely on the IV Administrator(s) to exercise judgment during the course of treatment. I acknowledge that I have been given the opportunity to discuss the nature and purpose of the treatment; and the risks, complications and consequences associated with the procedure. My questions have all been answered in terms I understand. I am aware of the risks and potential side effects if l undergo hydration therapy. I have truthfully answered all questions regarding my medical history and have told the staff about any and all prescription drugs I take, as well as any street or recreational drugs. Not telling the staff about your medical issues or drug use can lead to complications. I acknowledge that I am responsible for any medical care I have directly or indirectly related to my hydration therapy treatment. If there is an allergic reaction or otherwise, I agree that I am responsible for payment of my medical care. I hereby waive any and all claims.

Agreement to Arbitrate. It is understood that any dispute as to medical malpractice, that is as to whether any medical services rendered under this contract were unnecessary or unauthorized or were improperly, negligently or incompetently rendered, will be determined by submission to arbitration as provided by Utah law, and not by a lawsuit or resort to court process, except as Utah law provides for judicial review of arbitration proceedings. Both parties to this contract, by entering into it, are voluntarily giving up their constitutional right to have any such dispute decided in a court of law before a jury, and instead are accepting the use of binding arbitration.

All Claims Must be Arbitrated. It is the intention of the parties that this agreement shall col
existing or subsequent claims or controversies whether in tort, contract or otherwise, and shall bind all parties whose claims mav arise out of or in any way relate to treatment or services provided or not provided by the below identified physician, medical group or association, their partners, associates, associations, corporations, partnerships, employees, agents, clinics, and/or providers (collectively herein referred to as "Physician") to a patient, including any spouse or heirs of the patient and any children, whether born or unborn at the time of the occurrence giving rise to any claim. In the case of any pregnant mother, the term "patient" herein shall mean both the mother and the mother's expected child or children. Filing by Physician of any action in any court by the Physician to collect any fee from the patient shall not waive the right to compel arbitration of any malpractice claim. However, following the assertion of any claim against Physician, any fee dispute, whether or not the subject of any existing court action, shall also be resolved by arbitration. Procedures and Applicable Law. A notice or demand for arbitration must be communicated in writing by U.S. mail, postage prepaid, to all parties, describing the claim against Physician, the amount of damages sought, and the names, addresses and telephone numbers of the patient, and (if applicable) his or her attorney. The parties shall thereafter select an arbitrator to preside over the matter. Both parties agree the arbitration shall be governed pursuant to the Utah Uniform Arbitration Act, Utah Code Title 78B. The prevailing party shall be entitled to recovery of attorney's fees, and all costs, fees, and expenses associated with dispute.

Severability Provision. In the event any provision(s) of this Agreement is declared void and/or unenforceable, such provisions) shall be deemed severed there from and the remainder of this agreement enforced in accordance with Utah and federal law.

My signature below confirms that:
1. I am 18 years or older and am of sound legal mind to authorize and consent to the use of
hydration therapy.
2. The procedure set forth above has been adequately explained to me by my IV Administrator.
3. I have received all the information and explanation I desire concerning the procedure.
4. This document is intended to serve as confirmation of informed consent for hydration
therapy. If I mislead Dr. J's Infusion Therapy for any of the reasons mentioned above, by signing below I fully understand and take responsibility for the post treatment consequences.
6. I give my full informed consent for I.V. Hydration Therapy.
7. I have been given the option to speak to a Physician/Nurse Practitioner/Physician Assistant in regards to my IV treatment..</string>


    <string name="msg_no_internet">No Internet Connection: Please use your network to connect to the Internet..</string>
</resources>